chicagovps.net 2011-01-05

# Privacy Policy Our Commitment To Privacy

Privacy Policy
Our Commitment To Privacy
Your privacy is important to ChicagoVPS. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice
explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your
information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our
website.
ChicagoVPS reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. Such changes,
modifications, additions or deletions shall be effective immediately upon posting on-line at this
location. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this site and this
Policy periodically and to be aware of any modifications. You may identify whether
ChicagoVPS has revised this Privacy Policy by noting the "Effective Date" above. Your
continued use of the site after such modifications will constitute your: (a) acknowledgment of the
modified Policy; and (b) agreement to abide and be bound by the modified Policy. If you do not
agree to these terms, please do not access or use this site.
Types of Information Collected
In order to better provide you with our numerous services, we collect two types of information
about our users: Personal Information and Non-Personal Information.
Personal Information
When you order services through ChicagoVPS, we request certain personally identifiable
information from you on our order form to us to allow us to process your order, provide you with
the services you order from us, and to provide ongoing technical support for your account. You
must provide contact information (such as name, email, phone number, and address) and
financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). By purchasing our services,
you agree to provide and maintain accurate, complete and updated information.
After you have ordered our services, we may be in communication with you about your account.
These communications are essential to our relationship with you and to our ability to provide you
with quality services that are responsive to your needs. As a result, we may maintain information
about our communications with you for future use.
Disclosure of Personal Information
We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to provide
service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent
necessary to provide service. In the event that this policy changes, we will provide you with an
opportunity to opt out or otherwise prohibit the disclosure of your information to third parties for
any purpose other than your ordering and ongoing use of our services.

We do not sell, trade, or rent your Personal Information to others. We do provide some of our
services through contractual arrangements with affiliates, services providers, partners and other
third parties. We and our service partners use your Personal Information to operate our sites and
to deliver our services. For example, we must release your credit card information to the card-
issuing bank to confirm payment for products and services purchased on this site or release your
address information to the delivery service to deliver products that you ordered.
Occasionally, ChicagoVPS may be required by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide
Personal Information to the appropriate governmental authorities. We will disclose Personal
Information upon receipt of a court order or subpoena or to cooperate with a law enforcement
investigation. We fully cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use
ChicagoVPS services for illegal activities. We reserve the right to report to law enforcement
agencies any activities that ChicagoVPS in good faith believe to be unlawful.
ChicagoVPS may also use the Personal Information collected to contact customers regarding
important changes to our site, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable.
You will be given the opportunity to notify us of your desire not to receive these offers through
our client portal or by sending an email request at legal@chicagovps.net.
Non-Personal Information
ChicagoVPS collects tracking data when users visit our websites. Whenever you request a page
through your browser, navigation data such as your IP address, browser and version, operating
system, date and time and the site from which you came are stored in a log file. We use this data
to analyze visitors' use of our site in order to make improvements to our site.
Disclosure of Non-Personal Information
ChicagoVPS may share this anonymous traffic and demographic information in aggregate form
with other business partners. We do not share any information with anyone that can identify an
individual user.
Cookies
A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a users computer for record-keeping purposes.
ChicagoVPS may use both session ID cookies and/or persistent cookies. We use session cookies
to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close your
browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can
remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browsers help file.
Our Commitment To Data Security
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of
information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to

safeguard and secure the information we collect online. The ChicagoVPS website uses industry-
standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption on all web pages where personal information is
required. When entering Personal Information, we strongly recommend an SSL-enabled web
browser.
Our Commitment To Children's Privacy
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never
collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no
part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.
Access To Your Personal Information
You always have access to the information we have about you. To review and update your
personal contact information, simply log into our client portal. You may also email
billing@chicagovps.net to have the information changed.
Questions
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings
with this site, please contact us by sending an email to: legal@chicagovps.net
